天哪，我的脚都快炸裂了！
Oh my God, my feet are bursting!
¡Ay, Dios mío, se me revientan los pieses!
乔利在哪里？
Where is the Jolly?
¿Dónde está la Jolly?
¡ 快乐！
¡Jolly!
哦，我多么讨厌迟到。
Oh, how I hate tardiness.
Ay, como odio los impuntuales.
还有那些迟到的人。
And those who arrive late too.
Y los que llegan tarde también.
哦，我也是，苏珊娜。
Oh, me too, Susana.
Ay, yo también, Susana.
当时你在哪里？
Where were you?
¿Dónde estabas?
我很抱歉，我刚刚在车里迷路了，我跟着电话里的西班牙女士，她告诉我......
I apologize, I just got lost in the car, I followed the Spanish woman I have on the phone who told me...
Te pido perdón, es que me perdí con el auto, seguí por la española que tengo en el teléfono que me decía...
右转，转到达目的地！
Turn right, turn reaching your destination!
¡Gira a la derecha, gira llegando a su destino!
您确定他想向您推荐这份工作吗？
Are you sure he wants to present this job to you?
¿Estás segura que te quiere presentar este trabajo?
是的，你知道我现在是寡妇，我必须工作。
And yes, and you know that now I am a widow, I have to work.
Y si, y vos sabes que ahora soy viuda, tengo que trabajar.
此外，选拔通知还要求招聘一名按摩师和公用事业工人。
In addition, the selection notice asking for a masseuse and utility worker.
Además, el aviso de la selección pidiendo masajista y utilista.
但如果你在没有授权的情况下一直开车
but if you wheel all the time if you don't have authorization
pero si una rueda todo el tiempo si no tienes autorización
我怎么知道你有车？
How will I know that you have a car?
¿Cómo voy a saber que vos tenés auto?
但你必须知道这一点。
But you have to know it.
Pero tenés que saberlo.
某物？
Something?
¿Algo?
表明你自己的身份？
Identify yourself?
¿Identifíquese?
我是 Susana Espadafuchile，我来是为了……
I am Susana Espadafuchile, I come for the notice of...
Soy Susana Espadafuchile, vengo por el aviso de...
女按摩师
a masseuse
un masajista.
我是乔利拉，朋友，因为我很有用，所以我来作为一个道具。
And I am Jolila, friend, and since I am very useful, I come as a prop.
Y yo soy Jolila, amiga, y como soy muy útil, vengo de utilero.
他们将必须向我提供完成中学教育的分析证书。
They are going to have to present me with an analytical certificate of completed secondary education.
Me van a tener que presentar documento certificado analítico de estudios secundarios completos.
无债尿样、税、疫苗手册
Debt-free urine sample, tax, vaccine booklet
muestra de orina libre deuda, impositivo, libreta de vacuna
和一些用于安全的克雷蒙斯。
and some cremones for security.
y unas cremonas para el de seguridad.
我们什么都不知道，我们对这一切一无所知，但他们什么也没告诉我们。
We didn't know anything, we don't have anything about all that, but they didn't tell us anything.
Nosotros no sabíamos nada, no tenemos nada de todo eso, pero no nos dijeron nada.
他们将无法进入。
They will not be able to enter.
No van a poder ingresar.
¡转动帕拉霍伊！
¡Turna para hoy!
稍后见！
See you later!
¡Hasta luego!
你什么时候让我们过去？
When are you going to let us pass?
¿Cuándo nos va a dejar pasar?
维吉兰特先生，我想问你一件事，因为我们现在不知道如何离开这里。
Mr. Vigilante, I want to ask you something because we don't know how to get out of here now.
Señor vigilante, le quiero preguntar una cosa porque nosotros no sabemos ahora cómo salir de acá.
我们能有什么邦迪？
What bondi can we have?
¿Qué bondi le podemos tomar?
妈妈你看，我会解释的。
Look mom, I'll explain.
Mira mami, te explico.
你看到你进来的地方了吗？
Did you see where you came in?
¿Viste por donde entraste?
你来到这里，你在那里看到那条路。
You come here, you see that path, there.
Te venís hasta acá, ves el camino aquel, allá.
看到那座淡蓝色的建筑了吗？
Do you see the light blue building?
¿Ves el edificio celeste?
嗯，入口处就是选定的组。
Well, there at the entrance is the selected group.
Bueno, ahí en la entrada está el colectivo seleccionado.
如果你愿意的话就在那里。
There if you want.
Ahí si querés.
距离您有半个街区，198、293，您还有 Belgrano Sur 车站，如果没有，请穿过高速公路……
You have half a block away, 198, 293, you also have the Belgrano Sur station, and if not, cross the highway and...
Tenés a media cuadra, el 198, el 293, tenés la estación del Belgrano Sur también, y si no, cruzá la autopista y...
他们进入了我的身体。
They got into me.
Se me metieron.
他们进入了我的身体。
They got into me.
Se me metieron.
安全？
Security?
¿Seguridad?
他们进入了我的身体。
They got into me.
Se me metieron.
安全？
Security?
¿Seguridad?
他们在哪里？
Where are they?
¿Dónde están?
他们正在西方。
They are having the West.
Están teniendo a la Oeste.
有两个，有两个，都是塞满的。
There are two, there are two, they are stuffed.
Son dos, son dos, están metidas de peluche.
去吧，傻瓜，去吧，去吧。
Go pa' allá, fool, go pa' allá.
Anda pa' allá, bobo, anda pa' allá.
是的，这是一座重要的建筑。
Yes, it is an important building.
Sí, es un edificio importante.
不，看看帕普罗和甜筒，全是来自天堂的奶油。
No, look at the papurro and the cone that comes all cream from heaven.
No, mira el papurro y el cucurucho que viene todo de crema del cielo.
嗯，非常感谢。
Well, thank you very much.
Bueno, muchísimas gracias.
你好吗？
How are you doing?
¿Cómo les va?
一切都好吗？
All good?
¿Todo bien?
它们也非常美丽。
They are also very beautiful.
También son muy hermosas.
我自我介绍一下，我叫Tolosa，负责AFA财产。
I introduce myself, my name is Tolosa, I am in charge of the AFA property.
Me presento, mi nombre es Tolosa, soy el encargado del predio de la AFA.
好吧，我实际上是主人。
Well, I'm practically the owner.
Bueno, prácticamente soy el dueño.
我猜你们是来工作的，对吗？
I imagine you guys come for work, is that correct?
Me imagino que ustedes vienen por el trabajo, ¿es así?
是的，我是一名按摩师，她是一名道具师。
Yes, I am a masseuse and she is a prop artist.
Sí, yo soy masajista y ella, utilerista.
好吧，让我们从最基本的开始。
Ok, let's start with the most basic.
Ok, vamos a empezar por lo más básico.
我需要你把你的简历发给我。
I need you to send me your resume.
Necesito que me entren su currículum.
我的意思是我需要查看凭证，知道你们是经过培训的人。
I mean I need to see a credential, know that you are the trained people.
Me refiero al necesito ver una credencial, saber que son ustedes las personas capacitadas.
我们手头有简历
We have the resume at hand
el currículum lo tenemos a mano
没关系，你不理解我，因为我已经独自度过了很多时间。
It's okay, you don't understand me, because I've spent a lot of time alone.
No pasa nada, no me entiendes, porque yo lo he pasado mucho tiempo solo.
但这是卡吗？
But is that the card?
¿Pero ese es el carné?
卡片。
The card.
El carné.
我有，但是过期了。
I had it, but it expired.
Yo tenía, pero se me venció.
我要派他们去和两个我非常爱的人谈谈。
I'm going to send them to talk to two people I love very much.
Voy a mandarlas hablar con dos personas que quiero muchísimo.
爸爸、马里托和我还想告诉你们，里奥·梅西的电话响了
daddy and marito and I also want to tell you for a second that Leo Messi's phone is ringing
el daddy y marito y además quiero decirle un segundo que está sonando el teléfono a Leo Messi
一个吻。
A kiss.
Un beso.
你好，队长。
Hello, captain.
Hola, capitán.
不，我的一些女孩朋友。
No, some girls friends of mine.
No, unas chicas amigas mías.
你用香水做了什么？
What did you do with the perfume?
¿Qué hiciste con el perfume?
是我委托你的。
That I commissioned you.
Que yo te encargué.
我正在使用它，马特奥。
I'm kind of using it, Mateo.
Como que lo estoy usando, Mateo.
等一下。
Give me a second.
Dame un segundo.
马特奥如何使用他？
How does Mateo use him?
¿Cómo que le usa Mateo?
去年西罗也发生了同样的事情。
Last year the same thing happened with Ciro.
El año pasado le pasó el mismo con Ciro.
这是第一个任务。
It is the first mission.
es la primera misión.
对于工作通知。
For the job notice.
Por el aviso del trabajo.
哦，是的，为了工作。
Oh yes, for work.
Ah, sí, para el trabajo.
我们正在寻找马里托和大卫。
We are looking for Marito and David.
Estamos buscando a Marito y a David.
我还没有结婚，我还小。
I am not marital, I am small.
No soy marital, soy chiquitabia.
哦，琪琪！
Oh, chiqui!
¡Ay, chiqui!
大姑娘的亲戚！
Relative of the big girl!
¡Pariente de la chiquile gran!
他们同名同姓，是亲戚。
They have the same name, relative.
Es que se llaman igual, pariente.
但我不认为它很小，我认为它很大。
But I don't see it as very small, I see it as quite big.
Pero yo no lo veo muy chiquito, lo veo bastante grande.
不，我是 AFA 主席。
No, I am the president of the AFA.
No, soy el presidente de la AFA.
你想让我给你颈部按摩一下放松一下吗？我该怎么办？
Do you want me to give you a relaxing massage here on your neck, what would I do?
¿Quiere que le dé una masaja relajante acá en el cuello, que lo dejaría?
不，我不需要任何东西。
No, I don't need anything.
No, no necesito nada.
去看马里托和爸爸。
Go see Marito and Daddy.
Vayan a ver a Marito y a Daddy.
你也不需要雕刻吗？
You don't need a sculpt either?
¿Una esculpidad tampoco necesitas?
我不需要任何东西。
I don't need anything.
No necesito nada.
去更衣室。
Go to the locker room.
Vayan al vestuario.
这是你的决赛吗？
Is it your final?
¿Es tu definitiva?
如果您不想按摩，请。
Please, if you didn't want the massage.
Por favor, si no quiso el masaje.
再见，总统。
See you later, president.
Hasta luego, presidente.
祝你好运，是吗？
Good luck, huh?
Que le vaya bien, ¿eh?
愿我们都赢。
May we all win.
Que ganemos todas.
你是永久的吗？
Have you been permanent?
¿Habéis estado permanente?
没什么，没什么。
Nothing, nothing.
Nada, nada.
就像奥尔维娜准备战争一样
As in Olvina prepared for war
Como en Olvina preparado pa' la guerra
谢谢，梅西。
Thanks, Messi.
Gracias, Messi.
谢谢，巴尔巴。
Thanks, Barba.
Gracias, Barba.
谢谢，奇奇。
Thanks, Chiqui.
Gracias, Chiqui.
你在这里做什么？
What are you doing here?
¿Qué hacen ustedes acá?
你在这里做什么？
What are you doing here?
¿Qué hacen ustedes acá?
我们在等丹尼和马里托，因为那是更衣室。
We are waiting for Dani and Marito because it is the locker room.
Estamos esperando a Dani y a Marito porque es el vestuario.
你不能在这里，因为我是导演。
You can't be here because I'm the director.
no pueden estar acá ustedes porque no porque yo soy el director
我向每位球员提供阿根廷足球、阿根廷足协、阿根廷足协的阴谋。
of cabals of Argentine football, of the AFA, of the Argentine Football Association, I offer to each player.
de cábalas del fútbol argentino, de la AFA, de la Asociación del Fútbol Argentino, le ofrezco a cada jugador.
一系列目录供他们选择，因此我们赢得了决赛、美洲杯和世界杯。
a series of catalogs for them to choose from and thanks to that we won the final, the Copa América and the World Cup.
una serie de catálogos para que ellos puedan elegir y gracias a eso ganamos la finalísima, la Copa América y la Copa del Mundo.
你不能坐在这里！
You can't be sitting here!
¡No puedes estar sentada acá!
卡巴拉主任先生，我有自己的卡巴拉。
Mr. Kabbalah Director, I have my own Kabbalah.
Señor director de cábalas, yo tengo mi propia cábala.
你不知道处罚吗？
You don't know the penalties?
¿Vos no sabés los penales?
我交叉手指，触摸我的左乳房。
I cross my fingers and touch my left breast.
Yo cruzo las dedas y me toco el seno izquierdo.
如果我接住了它，我就会触碰另一只。
And if I catch it, I touch the other one.
Y si me copo, me toco el otro.
发生什么事了？
What's happening?
¿Qué pasa?
发生什么事了？
What's happening?
¿Qué pasa?
我不相信那些东西，我更……不，不，你必须相信。
I don't believe in those things, I'm more... No, no, you have to believe.
No creo en esas cosas, yo soy más... No, no, tienes que creer.
之前我还以为...
Before I thought that...
Antes pensé que...
那是一条鳟鱼。
It was a trout.
Era un trucho.
现在呢？
And now?
¿Y ahora?
两条鳟鱼！
Two trouts!
¡Dos truchos!
你好你好。
Hello hello.
Hola, hola.
向所有认识我的人问好。
Greetings to all who know me.
Saludos a todos los que me conocen.
游戏是《Good Envole》。
The game is Good Envole.
El partido es Buen Envole.
是的，这确实是一场艰难的比赛，我们做了我们这一周所做的工作。
Yes, it really was a difficult game, we did what we worked on during the week.
Sí, realmente fue un partido difícil, hicimos lo que trabajamos en la semana.
你在那里做什么？
And what are you doing there?
¿Y estas qué hacen ahí?
把他们救出来会很昂贵
it's going to be expensive to get them out
que va a ser caro ya a sacarlas
他们在这里做什么？
What are they doing here?
¿Qué hacen acá?
没什么，先生。
Nothing, sir.
Nada, señorito.
不不。
No no.
No, no.
我们正在等马里托和爸爸。
We are waiting for Marito and Daddy.
Estamos esperando a Marito y a Daddy.
我100岁了。
I am 100.
Yo soy 100.
多少？
How much?
¿Cuánto?
100.
社区经理。
Community manager.
是的，从选择来看。
Yes, from the selection.
Sí, de la selección.
我帮助玩家，你用 Facebook、Instagram、TikTok 上传文字，然后输入……
I help players, you upload type with Facebook, Instagram, TikTok, and type...
Ayudo a los jugadores, subicas tipo con Facebook, Instagram, TikTok, y tipo...
不，我带着签名。
No, I'm with the autographs.
No, yo estoy con los autógrafos.
谁？
Whose?
¿De quién?
入选者的签名。
The autographs of the selection.
Los autógrafos de la selección.
我的意思是，我的笔迹很好，而且他们也提供给我们，所以我做出了选择。
I mean, I have good handwriting and they have supplied us, so I make the selection.
O sea, tengo buena letra y ellos nos han abasto, así que hago las de la selección.
签名都找到了，除了亚历克西斯·麦卡利斯特的签名，我也没有得到。
The autographs are located, except for Alexis McAllister's, which I don't get too.
ubicados los autógrafos, salvo el de Alexis McAllister que no me sale también.
哪一个效果好呢？
And which one turns out well?
¿Y cuál que sale bien?
玛丽亚的面条。
Maria's Noodle.
El de Fideo de María.
像 Fideo 那样做。
Do it like Fideo.
Hacelo al de Fideo.
他们的名字是什么？
What are their names?
¿Cómo son sus nombres?
水和洒红节。
Water and Holi.
Su y Xoli.
好的。
GOOD.
Bien.
为了你...是的。
For you... Yes.
Para tú... Sí.
还有朱莉……是的。
And Jolie... Yes.
Y Jolie... Sí.
玛丽亚充满爱的视频。
María's video with love.
El video de María con cariño.
阿雷
Arre
Arre.
瞧，那是超级可爱的。
Look, it was super cute.
Mira, quedó supercuta.
一个版本，一个版本。
A ver, a ver.
哦，是一样的！
Oh, it's the same!
¡Ay, es igual!
玛丽亚的面条是什么？
What is Maria's noodle?
¿Cuál es el fideo de María?
什么是面条？
What is the noodle?
¿Cuál es el fideo?
而且都是一样的，都是一样的。
And it's the same, it's the same.
Y es igual, es igual.
好吧，好吧，我把它框起来并说这是视频。
Well, okay, I frame it and say it's the video.
Bueno, está bien, yo lo enmarco y digo que es el vídeo.
是的？
Yeah?
¿Sí?
你也代表球员签署支票吗？
Do you also sign checks on behalf of the players?
¿Firmás cheque también de parte de los jugadores?
是的当然。
Yes of course.
Sí, por supuesto.
哦，好吧，那我们谈谈吧。
Oh well, let's talk then.
Ah, bueno, pues hablamos entonces.
我们来了，我们来了！
Here we go, here we go!
¡Aquí vamos, aquí vamos!
哦！
Oh!
¡Ay!
这是谁？
And who is this?
¿Y esta quién es?
是的！
Yeah!
¡Sí!
比如是谁？
Like who is it?
¿Cómo que quién es?
我是珍妮！
I'm Jenny!
¡Soy la Jenny!
我是河童！
I am the Kappa!
¡Soy la Kappa!
正确的老板。
The right boss.
La jefa derechada.
我们计划去参加下一届世界杯。
We plan to go to the next World Cup.
Nosotros pensamos ir al próximo mundial.
是的？
Yeah?
¿Sí?
因为？
Because?
¿Por qué?
是的，你必须跟我说话。
Yes, you have to talk to me.
Sí, tiene que hablar conmigo.
我要把那面写着……的旗帜擦干。
I'm going to dry the flag that says...
Yo voy a secar la bandera que diga...
苏西礼物。
Susy present.
Susy presente.
我还要带另一张上面写着“朱莉”的，因为我要陪你一起去。
And I'm going to bring another one that says Jolie too because I'm going to accompany you.
Y yo voy a llevar otra que diga Jolie también porque te voy a acompañar.
当然，我建立了一个爸爸派。
Of course, I make a dad faction.
Claro, yo hago una facción de papá.
欧莱，欧莱，欧莱，欧莱！
Olé, olé, olé, olé!
¡Olé, olé, olé, olé!
奥莱，奥莱 奥莱，奥莱
Olé, olé Olé, olé
奥莱，奥莱，奥莱！
Olé, olé, olé!
¡Olé, olé, olé!
嘿！
Hey!
¡Olé!
所以是的。
So yes.
Así sí.
奥莱，奥莱，奥莱！
Olé, olé, olé!
¡Olé, olé, olé!
你必须更新。
You have to update.
Hay que actualizar.
听着，我们开始吧？
Listen, let's get started?
Escucha, ¿vamos a empezar?
现在我不打算提他了，我已经想去胡安娜那里了。
Now I'm not going to mention him, I already want to go to Juana.
Ahora no le voy a mencionar, ya quiero ir a la Juana.
但她生了！
But she gave birth!
¡Pero se parió!
哦，看看谁绑了我！
Oh, look who's tying me up!
¡Ay, mire quién atame en papos!
我可以相信！
I can believe it!
¡Me lo puedo creer!
我可以相信，我发誓！
I can believe it, I swear!
¡Me lo puedo creer, te juro!
科索特怎么样了？
How's Coshote doing?
¿Cómo anda Coshote?
场地！
Field!
¡Cámpola!
它是第一名吗？
Is it number one?
¿Es el número uno?
不，我是吉吉奥特·科波拉。
No, I'm Gigiote Coppola.
No, soy Gigiote Coppola.
不，科吉奥特·科波拉。
No, Coggiote Coppola.
啊，好吧，但是变调夹来自变调夹，这是变调夹。
Ah, well, but capo comes from capo, this is a capo.
Ah, bueno, pero capo la viene de capo, esto es un capo.
这是真的。
It's true.
Es verdad.
你是日本人吗？
Are you a Japanese for...?
¿Usted es un japon para...?
第一名就是你！
Number one is you!
¡El número uno es usted!
你现在还这样做吗？
Do you still do that?
¿Usted sigue haciendo eso?
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
¿Qué hace?
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
¿Qué hace?
这个是做什么的？
What does this one do?
¿Qué hace este?
起来吧！
Getting up!
¡El levantarse!
哎呀，我不会解除你的痛苦！
My, I won't lift your suffering!
¡Mis, a tu sufriste no levanto!
现在我有一家代理机构，科波拉集团，专门为足球运动员提供代理服务。
Today I have an agency, Copola Group, which is dedicated to representing soccer players.
Yo hoy tengo una agencia, Copola Group, que se dedica a representar futbolistas.
举办活动。
Make events.
Hacer eventos.
正是我们所需要的。
Just what we need.
Justo lo que necesitamos.
我们需要一个经理。
We need a manager.
Nosotras necesitamos un manager.
你打球吗？
Do you play ball?
¿Ustedes juegan a la pelota?
不，不是球。
No, not the ball.
No, a la pelota no.
但我们是来找工作的，如果我们见面，我们需要一个了解这个数字的人，我们理解。
But we came for a job and if we meet, we need someone who understands the number, we understand.
Pero vinimos por un trabajo y si quedamos, necesitamos a alguien que entienda el número, nosotros entendemos.
但更了解他是一名经理。
But someone who understands more that he was a manager.
Pero alguien que entienda más que era manager.
但我的收费很高。
But my fees are high.
Pero mis honorarios son elevados.
利润各占50%。
of the profits, 50% each.
de las ganancias, el 50% cada uno.
而损失中，100%是你的。
And of the losses, 100% is for you.
Y de las pérdidas, el 100% es para ustedes.
损失。
The loss.
La pérdida.
100% 对我们来说。
100% for us.
100% para nosotros.
确实如此。
Deal indeed.
Trato de hecho.
我会给你留一张小卡片，很快再见。
I'll leave you a little card and see you soon.
Le dejo una tarjetita y nos vemos próximamente.
再见，老板！
Goodbye, boss!
¡Adiós, capo!
多么华丽啊！
How gorgeous!
¡Qué hermoso!
你怎么把它搞砸了？
How do you screw it up?
¿Cómo lo cagas?
这是萨拉米香肠。
It's a salami.
Es un salame.
这是T和M。
This is the T and the M.
Esto es la T y la M.
噢，我们在这里问吧，因为玩家随时都会出现。
Oh, let's ask it here because at any moment the players appear.
Ay, pedímoslo acá a su que en cualquier momento aparecen los jugadores.
哦，你也这么认为吗？
Oh, do you think so?
Ay, ¿te parece?
我的胡子露出来了吗？
Are my mustaches showing through?
¿Se me traslucen los bigotes?
发生了什么？
What happened?
¿Qué pasó?
我们在做什么？
What are we doing?
¿Qué estamos haciendo?
我想我们去更衣室吧，他们正在踩草地。
I thought let's go to the locker room and they're stepping on the grass.
Pensé que vayan al vestor y están pisando el pasto.
谁在踩草地？
Who is stepping on the grass?
¿Quién está pisando el pasto?
他们正踩在草地上，小姐。
They're stepping on the grass, miss.
Están pisando el pasto, señorita.
那么，你想要什么，飞翔？
Well, what do you want, to fly?
Bueno, ¿qué querés, que vole?
让我飞吧，只要你愿意，我就飞。
Let me fly, if you want I'll fly.
Que vole, si querés volo.
而且她看起来很疯狂。
Plus she looks crazy.
Además ella se ve volada.
这是一种特殊的草。
This is a special grass.
Este es un pasto especial.
当我们成为冠军时，我们从卡塔尔引进了他。
We brought him from Qatar when we became champions.
Lo trajimos de Qatar cuando salimos campeones.
我不应该告诉这件事，但奇基塔皮亚把三块面包掉进了公文包里
I shouldn't have told this but Chiquitapia dropped three loaves of bread inside a briefcase
esto no tenía que haberlo contado pero a Chiquitapia se le cayeron tres panes adentro de un portafolio
我们用坎切罗种植，用矿泉水让它生长
and with the canchero we were planting and with mineral water we made it grow
y con el canchero estuvimos sembrando y con agua mineral hicimos crecer
是的，我们用三个面包完成了这一切。
Yes, with three loaves we did all this.
Sí, con tres panes hicimos todo esto.
我请求你，不要踩草地。
I ask you please, do not step on the grass.
Les pido por favor, no pisen el pasto.
请离开。
Please leave.
Retírense, por favor.
我们不踩它。
We don't step on it.
Nosotros no lo pisamos.
我们正在踩它。
We are stepping on it.
Lo estamos pisando.
好的，我去点酒吧。
Ok, I'll order the bar.
Ok, voy a pedir el bar.
酒吧喊道，我们无法准确地看到他们是否踏上比赛场地，但
the bar calls, we don't get to see precisely if they stepped on the playing field or not but
el bar llama, no llegamos a ver con precisión si pisaron o no el campo de juego pero
我需要你给我你的意见，胡安·巴勃罗。
I need you to give me your opinion, Juan Pablo.
Necesito que me de su opinión, Juan Pablo.
都是你的。
All yours.
Todo tuyo.
伙伴你说什么？
What do you say, partner?
¿Qué dices, compañero?
我认为有
I think there is
Creo que hay
这可能是非自愿的，但我们会看看他们的决定。
It could be involuntary, but we'll see what they decide.
Podría ser involuntaria, pero veremos qué deciden.
我们沿着为圣胡安设定的路线行驶。
We tread the line that is set for San Juan.
Nosotros pisamos la línea que se le pone a San Juan.
我这里有图像，慢动作可能会失真，但这里毫无疑问。
I have the image here, slow motion can distort, but there is no doubt here.
Tengo la imagen acá, la cámara lenta puede distorsionar, pero acá no hay ninguna duda.
但毫无疑问，波萨多。
But no doubt, Posado.
Pero ninguna duda, Posado.
确认的。
Confirmed.
Confirmado.
确认了，酒吧确认了，他们走上了比赛场。
confirmed, the bar confirms it, they stepped onto the playing field.
confirmado, lo confirma el bar, pisaron el campo de juego.
和？
And?
¿Y qué?
和？
And?
¿Y qué?
我们要抗议吗？
Are we going to have a protest?
¿Vamos a hacer una protesta?
因为我们在这里。
Because here we are.
Porque acá estamos.
做你想做的事。
Do what you want.
Hagan lo que quieran.
做你想做的事。
Do what you want.
Hagan lo que quieran.
来吧，来吧。
Go ahead, go ahead.
Adelante, adelante.
你是来看通知的吗？
Are you coming for the notice?
¿Ustedes vienen por el aviso?
我是一个丈夫。
I am a husband.
Yo soy marito.
哦，马里托！
Oh, Marito!
¡Ay, Marito!
国家队的吻神！
The kisser of the national team!
¡El besoqueño de la selección!
它被撕裂了！
It was torn!
¡Se le rasgó!
这是一次意外，是无意的。
It was an accident, it was unintentional.
Fue un accidente, fue sin querer.
那是因为胜利的喜悦。
It was because of the joy of victory.
Fue por la alegría del triunfo.
我是一个道具人。
I am a prop man.
Yo soy utilero.
现在我的助理来了。
Now my assistant is coming.
Ahora va a venir mi asistente.
卡鲁查！
¡Carucha!
啊，卡鲁查！
Ah, Carucha!
¡Ah, Carucha!
你好，卡鲁查！
Hello, Carucha!
¡Hola, Carucha!
哦，他也吻了你！
Oh, he kissed you too!
¡Ay, te dio un beso también!
当然！
Of course!
¡Claro!
谁来找通知的？
Who came for the notice?
¿Quién vino por el aviso?
我们俩。
Both of us.
Nosotras dos.
啊，很好。
Ah, good.
Ah, bien.
我是一名女按摩师。
I am a masseuse.
Yo es yo masajista.
很好，完美。
Good, perfect.
Bien, perfecto.
好吧，我们对你有什么看法？
Well, what do we think about you?
Bueno, ¿qué nos pensamos con vos?
一个美好的一天。
One fine day.
Un buen día.
你呢？
And you?
¿Y vos vos?
是的，和你在一起。
Yes, with you.
Sí, con vos.
来！
Come!
¡Venid!
哦，我有砍刀！
Oh, I have machetes!
¡Ay, yo tengo machetes!
好，好，好。
Good, good, good.
Bien, bien, bien.
这就是产品。
This is the product.
Es este el producto.
你的头发是什么做的？
What's making your hair?
¿Qué está poniendo el pelo?
一点奶油。
A little cream.
Un poquito de crema.
好吧，从玻璃上看永远不会坏。
Well, never bad from the glass.
Bien, nunca malo de la copa.
但这并不愚蠢。
But it's not stupid.
Pero no es coba.
你看到模因了吗？
Did you see the memes?
¿Viste los memes?
我看到了一切。
I saw everything.
Ví todo.
很强吧？
Strong, huh?
Fuerte, ¿eh?
我喜欢它，这就是为什么... 和理发师谈谈，我下次就像受审一样。
I liked it, that's why... Talk to the hairdressers, I'm like on trial next time.
Me gustó, por eso... Habla con los peruqueros, soy como en un juicio la próxima vez.
我看到了。
I saw it.
Lo vi.
好的，太好了。
Okay great.
Ok, perfecto.
我们来时，请带上糖果。
Take candy, as we come.
Toma caramelo, como venimos.
我
i
我不能对你撒谎。
I can't lie to you.
No te puedo mentir.
你吃多少？
How much are you eating?
¿Cuánto estás comiendo?
我们走吧。
Let's go.
Vamos.
32.
32个很多了。
32 is a lot.
32 es muchísimo.
糖又上升了一个档次。
Sugar is up a notch.
La azúcar está un pico arriba.
允许！
Permission!
¡Permiso!
¡哎呀哎呀！
¡Ey, ey, ey!
我
i
我死定了！
I'm dead dead!
¡Me muero muerto!
问我儿子，我不知道他在这里！
Ask my son, I didn't know he was here!
¡Pregúntame a mi hijo, yo no sabía que él estaba acá!
我要死了！
I'm dying!
¡Me muero!
当然！
Of course!
¡Claro!
多好的一个小伙子啊！
What a nice brat!
¡Qué lindo brato!
你能面对吗？
Can you face it?
¿Te puedes encarar?
多谢。
Thanks a lot.
Muchísimas gracias.
我来了。
I'm coming.
Ya vengo.
记住我告诉你的话。
Remember what I told you.
Acordate lo que te dije.
我的儿子马里托，你在叫我吗？
my son marito, were you calling me?
mi hijo marito, me llamabas?
唐·保罗，唐·保罗，我快要死了，我以其中的乐趣发誓。
Don Paul, Don Paul, I'm dying, I swear by the pleasure of it.
Don Paul, Don Paul, yo me muero, te juro por el gusto yo.
不，不，来自保罗。
No, no, from Paul.
No, no, de Paul.
我差点认不出你了。
I almost don't recognize you.
Yo casi no te reconozco.
你在这里做什么？
What are you doing here?
¿Qué hace acá?
你继续玩了吗？
Did you continue playing?
¿Seguió jugando?
这位被征召了，他是选拔的小引擎。
This one is called up, he is the little engine of the selection.
Este está convocado, es el motorcito de la selección.
小马达！
The little motor!
¡El motorcito!
如果我看到它，它就是一个引擎。
And if I see it, it's an engine.
Y si yo lo ve, es un motor.
兔子！
Rabbit!
¡Conejo!
因为你的头发我没认出你，因为我总是改变颜色。
I didn't recognize you because of your hair, because I always changed color.
Yo no te reconocía por el pelo, porque siempre cambié de color.
而且现在我看到他，他很安静。
And also now that I see him, he is very quiet.
Y además ahora que lo veo es que es muy calladito.
整天在球场上说话、说话。
And on the court all day talking, talking.
Y en la cancha todo el día hablando, hablando.
你在法庭上说什么？
What do you say on the court?
¿Qué dices en la cancha?
它们是游戏的东西，它们是两个不同的
They are things of the game, they are two different
son cosas del juego son dos diferentes
啊！
¡Ah!
是的，你看，她正在跑步作为道具，想要批准这个声音。
Yes, look, she is running as a prop and wanted to approve the voice.
Sí, mira, ella está postulante como utilera y quería aprobar la voz.
我是一名女按摩师。
And I am a masseuse.
Y yo soy masajista.
来吧，来吧，来吧。
Come, come, come.
Vení, vení, vení.
坐下
sit down
Sentate.
阿科斯塔，阿科斯塔。
Acostate, acostate.
小心点，这需要几个小时。
Be careful, it's worth hours.
Cuidado que valen horas.
是的！
Yeah!
¡Sí!
里面有多少涂鸦啊！
How much graffiti it has!
¡Cuánto graffiti que tiene!
但看看这条腿出来了什么。
But look at what this leg comes out with.
Pero mire lo que sale esta pierna.
它值多少钱，它说多少钱？
And what is it worth, how much does it say?
Y lo que vale, ¿cuánto dice?
我参加了急救课程。
I took a first aid course.
Hice curso de los primeros auxilios.
是的，第一次，然后第二次他们把她赶了出去。
Yes, the first ones, then the second one they kicked her out.
Sí, los primeros, después la segunda la echaron.
好吧，好吧，好吧。
Well, well, well.
Bueno, bueno, bueno.
我们来试试吧。
Let's try it.
Vamos a probarlo.
我卖吗？
Do I sell it?
¿Lo vendo?
是的，是的。
Yes, yes.
Sí, sí.
卖了，卖给大家了……
Sell ​​it, sell it to everyone...
Vendalo, vendalo a todos los...
噢，请不要这样对我，好吗？
Oh, please don't do that to me, okay?
Ay, por favor, no me hagas eso, ¿vale?
你在说什么？
What are you saying?
¿Qué dices?
如果你不来，我就买它。
And if you don't come, I'll buy it.
Y si no vienes, yo lo compro.
哦，拜托。
Oh, please.
Ay, por favor.
哦，拜托。
Oh, please.
Ay, por favor.
对不起！
Sorry!
¡Perdón!
对不起！
Sorry!
¡Perdón!
小心！
Careful!
¡Cuidado!
你不想！
You don't want to!
¡No quieres!
我会坚强的！
I will be strong!
¡Voy a ser fuerte!
我要疯了！
I'm going to be crazy!
¡Voy a ser loco!
不，疯了！
No, crazy!
¡No, loco!
它非常强大。
It's very strong.
Está muy fuerte.
非常强！
It's very strong!
¡Está muy fuerte!
哦，但是什么植物啊！
Oh, but what flora!
¡Ay, pero qué flora!
非常有电影感！
It's very cinema!
¡Es muy cine!
这对脚腹有好处所以看看这是什么
and this is good for the bellies of the feet so look what this is
y esto es bueno para las barris de los pies entonces mira lo que es esto
我们将为您加倍
and we will double it for you
y nosotros te la doblamos
她叠你的衣服！
She folds your clothes!
¡Ella te la dobla la ropa!
宁静，宁静，宁静，你，你，你，你。
Tranquilo, tranquilo, tranquilo, you, you, you, you.
Tranquilo, tranquilo, tranquilo, anda, anda, anda, anda.
哦，照顾好自己，我把它卖了，它会自杀的。
Oh, take care of yourself, I'll sell it, it's going to kill itself.
Ay, cuídate, yo me la vendo, se va a matar.
不不。
No no.
No, no.
我很高兴！
I'm happy!
¡Feliz estoy!
我是来参加按摩测试的。
I come for the massage test.
Vengo a la prueba de masajismo.
进来之前你洗脚了吗？
Did you clean your feet before coming in?
¿Te limpiaste los pies antes de entrar?
一个版本。
A ver.
是的，很干净。
Yes, it's clean.
Sí, está limpio.
请降低它。
Lower it please.
Bájalo, por favor.
你是谁？
Who are you?
¿Vos quién sos?
我是厨师。
I am the cook.
El cocinero soy.
哦，多好啊！
Oh, how good!
¡Ay, qué bien!
我会成为谁？
Who am I going to be?
¿Quién voy a ser?
清洁的那个？
The cleaning one?
¿El de limpieza?
哪里说你是清洁工？
And where does it say you're the cleaning guy?
¿Y por dónde dice que sos el de limpieza?
那里说哈贾。
There it says the haja.
Ahí dice la haja.
我还以为你是退役球员呢
I thought you were a retired player.
Pensé que eras un jugador retirado.
对不起。
Sorry.
Perdón.
你已经这样做了，因为清洁打蛋
and you are already doing it because cleaning beating eggs
y ya estás haciendo porque limpiando batiendo huevos
他们正在打扫卫生，因为这些孩子是猪圈。
They are cleaning because these kids are a pigsty.
Están limpiando porque estos chicos son un chiquero.
我增加辞职。
I increase my resignation.
Yo me aumento el renuncio.
好吧，你会怎么做？
Okay what would you do?
¿Está bien en qué harías?
厨师。
Chef.
Cocinero.
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
一年前我用它做了一个蛋糕？
I made a cake out of it a year ago?
¿Hice un bizcocho de él hace un año?
不。
No.
是的？
Yeah?
¿Sí?
你的结果如何？
And how did it turn out for you?
¿Y cómo te salió?
而且有点难，我还剪不了。
And it's a little hard, I can't cut it yet.
Y está un poco duro, no lo puedo cortar todavía.
我家里连镇纸都没有。
I don't even have it as a paperweight at home.
Lo tengo de pisapapel ni en casa.
啊，一年后。
Ah, after a year.
Ah, después de un año.
好吧，祝其他人好运，我要离开，因为我要去观看一部名为 Beykoz 的电视节目。
Well, good luck with the others, I'm leaving because I'm going to watch a TV show called Beykoz.
Bueno, escúchame suerte con los demás, que me voy porque voy a ver un programa de tele que se llama Beykoz.
让我们看看我是否学到了一些东西
Let's see if I learn something
a ver si aprendo algo
我想问你一个谜语。
I want to ask you a riddle.
Te quiero hacer una adivinanza.
电影的名字是什么？
What is the name of the movie?
¿Cómo se llama la película?
一个做蛋糕的人转而做choripanes。
that a man who made cakes switched to making choripanes.
que un señor que hacía tortas se pasó a hacer choripanes.
它叫什么？
What's it called?
¿Cómo se llama?
勒索者！
Extortist!
¡Extortista!
我个人很喜欢，不知道我是否理解了。
I personally liked it, I don't know if I understood it.
A mí personalmente me gustó, no sé si lo entendí.
很多，但我还是笑了。
a lot, but I laughed anyway.
mucho, pero me reí igual.
你笑了吗？
Did you laugh?
¿Te reíste?
这才是最重要的，快乐。
That's what counts, the joy.
Eso es lo que cuenta, la alegría.
你好吗？
How are you?
¿Qué tal?
很高兴见到你。
Nice to meet you.
Mucho gusto.
你做什么？
And what do you do?
¿Y vos qué hacés?
我是公交车司机。
I'm the bus driver.
Soy el chofer del micro.
啊！
¡Ah!
哦，我多么希望有一天能去坐公共汽车。
Oh, how I would like to go to the bus one day.
Ay, cómo me gustaría ir un día al micro.
您想去哪里？
Where would you like to go?
¿A dónde te gustaría ir?
哦，不，不，我只是处理它们，我把它们从酒店带到体育场。
Oh, no, no, I just handle them, I take them from the property to the stadium.
Ah, no, no, yo solo los manejo, los llevo del predio al estadio.
我是沿海航行。
I am cabotage.
Soy de cabotaje.
啊，我不知道那个地方，不过没关系。
Ah, I don't know that place, but it doesn't matter.
Ah, no conozco ese lugar, pero no importa.
你叫我按摩师吗？
Did you call me a masseuse?
¿Me dijiste masajista?
按摩师做按摩的时候真是太神奇了。
It's amazing when masseuses do massage.
Es increíble cuando los masajistas hacen masaje.
变调夹之后于基督之前 2700 年在中国出现
emerged in China 2700 years before Christ after the capo
surge en china 2700 años antes de cristo después la cejilla
他们进入现场，他们创造反射疗法，但当然，我们不必排除......
They enter the scene, they create reflexology, but of course, we do not have to rule out...
entran en la escena, crean la reflexología, pero claro, no tenemos que descartar...
当然，对希腊人来说，有所有的文化、体育文化、思想，但真正的现代按摩，19世纪的亨利·克林……
to the Greeks, of course, with all the culture, the physical culture, the mind, but the true modern massage, 19th century, Henry Kling...
a los griegos, claro, con toda la cultura, la cultura física, la mente, pero el verdadero masaje moderno, siglo XIX, Henry Kling...
瑞典人。
The Swede.
El sueco.
你看过关于按摩的那一篇吗？
Did you see the one about the massages?
¿Viste el de los masajes?
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
这是壮观的、巨大的、非常好的。
It is spectacular, tremendous, very good.
Es espectacular, tremendo, buenísimo.
我不敢相信你怎么知道这一切。
I can't believe how you know all that.
Yo no puedo creer cómo sabes todo eso.
更何况，事实上，对不起，我只是给自己留了一点空间。
What's more, in fact, excuse me, but I made a little space for myself.
Es más, de hecho, disculpame, pero me hice un huequito.
我要去公交车上读一点关于篮子虫的变态的知识。
I'm going to the bus to read a little about the metamorphosis of the basket bug.
Me voy al micro a leer un poquito sobre la metamorfosis del bicho canasto.
你有事吗？
Do you anything?
¿Vos cualquier cosa?
如果有人问起我的话。
If anyone asks about me.
Si alguien pregunta por mí.
你没看见我吗？
Didn't you see me?
¿No me viste?
这是一次完美的逃脱。
This is a perfect escape.
Esto que sea un escape perfecto.
超。
Chao.
嗨，事情怎么样？
Hi how are things?
Hola, ¿qué tal?
我是爸爸。
I'm Daddy.
Soy Daddy.
¡爸爸！
¡Daddy!
你是来应聘按摩师工作的吗？
Are you coming for the masseuse job?
¿Viene por el trabajo de masajista?
是的，要提供证据。
Yes, to give proof.
Sí, para dar la prueba.
我是一名有执照的按摩治疗师。
I am a licensed massage therapist.
Soy masajista matriculada.
嗯，他要去参加考试。
Well, he's going to take a test.
Bueno, se va a tomar una prueba.
哦真的吗？
Oh really?
¿En serio?
噢，多么美丽，谢谢。
Oh, how beautiful, thank you.
Ay, qué hermoso, gracias.
我把你想要的东西带到了这里。
I brought you here what you asked for.
Te traje acá lo que me pediste.
你不是马里托的助手吗？
Weren't you Marito's assistant?
¿Vos no eras el ayudante de Marito?
是的，还有 ADIAS 助理，他有工作……
Yes, and ADIAS assistant, who with a job...
Sí, y asistente de ADIAS, que con un trabajo...
这一个有两个缺口？
Two gaps in this one?
¿Dos laguras en este?
好吧，好吧。
Okay, okay.
Vale, vale.
参加测试。
Take the test.
Haz la prueba.
谢谢。
Gracias.
是的，我接受。
Yes, I take it.
Sí, me la toma.
抱歉，没有。
Sorry, no.
Sentimos, no.
很好，完美。
Good, perfect.
Bien, perfecto.
让我们看看，肌肉受伤后你给球员穿的第一件事是什么？
Let's see, what is the first thing you put on a player after a muscle injury.
A ver, que es lo primero que se le pone a un jugador después de una lesión muscular.
替补。
A substitute.
Un suplente.
很好，很有趣，快来实践一下
very good, very interesting, let's get to practice
muy bien, muy interesante, mejor vamos a la practica
你知道我没有骗你，对吗？
You know I'm not lying to you, right?
Sabe que yo no te miento, ¿eh?
我的意思是，波尔有外表，但你是最棒的。
I mean, Pol has an appearance, but you are superlative.
O sea, de Pol tiene facha, pero tu sos superlativo.
永远不要全身心投入到那部分的行动中。
Never dedicate yourself to acting on that part.
Nunca te dediques a actuar por esa parte.
我没有开始。
I didn't start.
No empecé.
又是同样的事情。
Again with the same thing.
Otra vez con lo mismo.
好吧，好吧。
Well, okay.
Bueno, ok.
买了糖...
Bought candy...
Comprado caramelo...
就在那里！
There it is!
¡Ahí está!
我要去买一只小鸭子。
I'm going to buy a duckling.
Voy a comprar un anadero.
允许！
Permission!
¡Permiso!
请！
Please!
¡Por favor!
你在说什么？
What are you saying?
¿Qué dices?
你叫我什么？
What are you calling me?
¿Qué me llamas?
那？
That?
¿Qué?
那？
That?
¿Qué?
我有看吗？
Did I watch it?
¿Lo puse a ver?
我发誓，他马上就要抓住我了。
I swear, he's about to grab me.
Te juro, me está por agarrar un surmen.
就这样！
That's all!
¡Eso es todo!
莱安德罗·帕雷德斯。
Leandro Paredes.
莱安德罗，莱安德罗。
Leandro, Leandro.
好吧，莱安德罗，莱安德罗。
Well, Leandro, Leandro.
Bueno, Leandro, Leandro.
我们带她来当按摩师。
We brought her in as a masseuse.
La trajimos como masajista.
我要去测试一下。
I'm going to give a test.
Voy a dar una prueba.
是的？
Yeah?
¿Sí?
它可以工作。
It can work.
Puede funcionar.
它可以工作。
It can work.
Puede funcionar.
我慢慢地做你。
I do you slowly.
Te hago despacito.
我从这里开始。
I start here.
Empiezo por acá.
如果你不想让洛佩兹碰你。
If you don't want the lópez to touch you.
Si no querés que te toque el lópez.
不，不，不。
No, no, no.
他有碰你的脖子吗？
Did he touch your neck?
¿Te tocó el cuello?
不，是腿。
No, the leg.
No, la pierna.
啊，腿。
Ah, the leg.
Ah, la pierna.
这是一个测试。
It's a test.
Es una prueba.
对于洛佩兹来说，他们是半个狂热分子。
With López they are half fanatics.
con el López son medio fanáticos.
你有喷雾吗？
Do you have spray?
¿Tienes spray?
你是喷子吗？
Are you spray?
¿Estás spray?
告诉他，告诉他，请告诉他！
Tell him, tell him, please tell him!
¡Decíle, decíle, por favor, decíle!
好吧，没关系。
OK that's fine.
Bueno, está bien.
但我喜欢他们为你描绘的方式，我喜欢它。
But I liked how they illustrated you, I like it.
Pero me gustaba como te ilusaron, me gusta.
很可爱。
It's lovely.
Es hermoso.
美丽的。
Beautiful.
Hermoso.
我将展示它。
I'm going to show it.
Lo voy a enseñar.
我会稍微解释一下。
I'm going to explain it a little.
Lo voy a explicar un poco.
我把它放在哪里？
Where do I put it?
¿Dónde le pongo?
在腿上。
On the legs.
En las piernas.
在腿上。
On the legs.
En las piernas.
这个会去吗？
Will this one go?
¿Esta irá?
但首先是腿
the legs but first
las piernas pero primero
活着的双胞胎要花多少钱或多或少？
How much will the living twin cost more or less?
¿Cuánto costará más o menos el gemelo que vive?
要知道。
To know.
Para saber.
我们阻止了它，是的。
We stopped it, yes.
Lo paramos, sí.
停下来，停下来。
Stop it, stop it.
Parala, parala.
不，这并不奇怪。
No, it's not strange.
No, no está rara.
我的爱是什么？
And what is this my love?
¿Y esto qué es mi amor?
谁对你做的？
Who did it to you?
¿Quién te lo hizo?
一个土豆。
A potato.
Una patata.
谁给你的？
Who gave it to you?
¿Quién te la dio?
这是接触水泥！
This is contact cement!
¡Esto es cemento de contacto!
我该如何将接触水泥涂在你身上？
How was I going to put the contact cement on you?
¿Cómo te iba a poner el cemento de contacto?
不能接触水泥，会硬的
There cannot be contact cement, it will be hard
No puede haber cemento de contacto, se la va a dejar dura
是的，基本上是的。
Yes, basically yes.
Sí, básicamente sí.
我有什么感觉，莱安德罗？
What did I feel, Leandro?
¿Qué sentí, Leandro?
我有什么感觉？
What did I feel?
¿Qué sentí?
事情稳定了一点，我们走吧。
It settles a little and let's go.
Se cala un poco y vamos.
就是这样，就是这样。
That's it, that's it.
Eso está, eso está.
走吧，走吧。
Let's go, let's go.
Vámonos, vámonos.
就是这样，就是这样，就是这样。
That's it, that's it, that's it.
Ya está, ya está, ya está.
抱歉，伙计们。
Sorry, guys.
Perdón, muchachos.
请。
please.
por favor.
跟我来。
Follow me.
Acompáñame.
我们走吧，我们走吧，我们走吧。
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Vámonos, vámonos, vámonos.
啊！
¡Ah!
¡ 柴苏！
¡  Chaisu!
¡Chaisu!
进展如何？
How did it go?
¿Cómo te fue?
好吧，好吧，但是我在尖端上涂的奶油有点问题。
Well, fine, but I had a little problem with the cream I put on the tip.
Bueno, bien, pero tuve un problemita con la crema que le puse en la punta.
不，不，不，不，不！
No, no, no, no, no!
¡No, no, no, no, no!
首先，他们对我所做的事情非常丑陋。
First, what they did to me is very ugly.
Primero, es muy feo lo que me hicieron.
我们对你做了什么？
What did we do to you?
¿Qué te hicimos?
第二个是法国。
And second, France.
Y segundo, Francia.
什么是透明的。
What is transparent.
Lo que es transparente.
那不好，我把他们介绍给球员了，我不喜欢他们的做法，丑陋。
That's not good, I introduced them to the players, I don't like what they did, ugly.
No está bueno eso, les presenté a los jugadores, no me gusta lo que hicieron, feo.
我们必须工作，我是寡妇，我必须工作
We have to work, I am a widow, I have to work
Nosotros tenemos que trabajar, yo soy viuda, tengo que trabajar
你必须准备、思考、很多事情。
You have to prepare, think, a lot of things.
Tienes que prepararte, piensa, un montón de cosas.
而且，我离开时什么也没有，最重要的是，没有夏天。
And besides, I'm leaving with nothing and, on top of that, without summer.
Y además me voy sin nada y encima sin verano.
再见。
Bye bye.
Adiós.
我告诉自己他们所说的话击中了我。
I tell myself that what they are saying hits me.
Me digo que me pega lo que están diciendo.
我们该怎么办？
What do we do?
¿Qué hacemos?
我已经要求了。
I already asked for it.
Ya me lo pedí.
哦，他多么爱啊。
Oh, how he loves.
Ay, qué ama.
电影院很好。
The cinema was good.
Era buena el cine.
你好，你吗？
Hello, you?
Hola, ¿tú?
嗯，不可能。
Well, it can't be.
Bueno, no puede estar.
当我小的时候，我和妈妈在你的旅馆里看过你……
I watched you at your hotel with my mom when I was...
te miraba a su hotel con mi mamá cuando era...
当我还小的时候，现在他这么做了，我就不能在场了。
When I was little and now that he does this, I can't be present.
Cuando era chiquito y ahora que hace esto, yo no puedo estar presente.
但是，嘿，我很高兴孩子们参加了那里并且他们玩得很开心。
But hey, I'm very happy that the kids participated there and that they had a good time.
Pero bueno, me alegro mucho que hayan participado los chicos ahí y que les han pasado bien uno.
花一点时间做这一切，然后给你一个大大的吻
a little while doing all that and give you a big kiss
un ratito haciendo todo eso y darte un beso grande
下一位可能会出现。
The next one may be present.
la próxima puede estar presente.
再见，一个吻。
Bye, a kiss.
Chau, un beso.